(Sheldon:)Although copyright law would allow me
to quote snippets in the context of a review.
I'm glad you're feeling better.
(Bernadette:)Me too.
But if I'd known we were gonna be dancing,
I would've wore my flats.
- Well, this turned out pretty well, huh?
- Yeah, I think so.
(Raj:)I agree. That is, if you've never
been to or heard of a party before.
(Amy:)If you'd let me pierce your brain
with a hot needle in the right place...
(Amy:)...you'd be happy all the time.
Penny, I have a couple of questions
about your closet.
(Sheldon:)Is there any reason
you're keeping this dead goldfish?
(Penny:)Damn, I forgot to feed him.
(Penny:)And that I had him.
(Sheldon:)Well, now, did you also have a dog?
(Sheldon:)Because I found what appears to be
a battery-operated chew toy...
(Penny:)Party's over! Party's over!